[
    {
        "id": 0,
        "section": 1,
        "description": "Features of the language, pronunciation, the alphabet, and simple greetings.",
        "questions" : [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "question": "Which is the correct lenition of \"Dear friend\"?",
                "choices": ["a cara", "a gcara", "a chara", "ah cara"],
                "correctAnswer": "a chara",
                "reason": "When addressing someone, add a séimhiú.",
                "state": "unanswered",
                "selectedAnswer": "",
                "category": "Eclipsis and Lenition",
                "isSubmitted": false
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "question": "How would you say \"the shoe\"?",
                "choices": ["tá bróg", "an bhróg", "ná bhróga", "mo bhróg"],
                "correctAnswer": "an bhróg",
                "reason": "Feminine nouns use the séimhiú.",
                "state": "unanswered",
                "selectedAnswer": "",
                "category": "Eclipsis and Lenition",
                "isSubmitted": false
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "question": "How would you say \"three cats\"?",
                "choices": ["trí chat", "tríuir chata", "ná cait trí", "an cait trí"],
                "correctAnswer": "trí chat",
                "reason": "Counting things of 2 to 6 takes a séimhiú.",
                "state": "unanswered",
                "selectedAnswer": "",
                "category": "Eclipsis and Lenition",
                "isSubmitted": false
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "question": "How would you say \"I am living in...\"?",
                "choices": ["Táim cóaní orm...", "Tá mé i mo cóaní i...", "Tá cóaní agam...", "Tá mé i mo chónaí i..."],
                "correctAnswer": "Tá mé i mo chónaí i...",
                "reason": "Possessive mo, do, agus a (my, yours, and his) get a séimhiú.",
                "state": "unanswered",
                "selectedAnswer": "",
                "category": "Eclipsis and Lenition",
                "isSubmitted": false
            },
            {
                "id": 5,
                "question": "How would you say \"You are in Dublin\"?",
                "choices": [
                    "Tá tú i mBaile Átha Cliath.", 
                    "Tá tú i Baile Átha Cliath.",
                    "Tá muid i mBaile Átha Cliath.", 
                    "Tá muid i Baile Átha Cliath."
                ],
                "correctAnswer": "Tá tú i mBaile Átha Cliath.",
                "reason": "Some prepositions (such as \"i\" meaing \"in\") are followed by the úrú. The city of Dublin does not have an article \"an\" meaing \"the\".",
                "state": "unanswered",
                "selectedAnswer": "",
                "category": "Eclipsis and Lenition",
                "isSubmitted": false
            },
            {
                "id": 6,
                "question": "Which is the correct conjugation of \"Your family\"?",
                "choices": [
                    "Tú teaghlach",
                    "Do teaghlach",
                    "A theaghlach",
                    "Do theaghlach"
                ],
                "correctAnswer": "Do theaghlach",
                "reason": "Mo (my), do (your), and a (his/her) get séimhiú.",
                "state": "unanswered",
                "selectedAnswer": "",
                "category": "Eclipsis and Lenition",
                "isSubmitted": false
            },
            {
                "id": 7,
                "question": "How would you say \"I am sitting\"?",
                "choices": [
                    "Tá mé i mo shuí",
                    "Tá mo shuí",
                    "Tá me i mo suí",
                    "Táimid inár suí"
                ],
                "correctAnswer": "Tá mé i mo shuí",
                "reason": "Mo (my), do (your), and a (his/her) get séimhiú. Literaly translation is \"I am in my sitting\".",
                "state": "unanswered",
                "selectedAnswer": "",
                "category": "Eclipsis and Lenition",
                "isSubmitted": false
            },
            {
                "id": 8,
                "question": "What is the correct translation for \"I was at work\"?",
                "choices": [
                    "Bí mé ag obair",
                    "Bhí mé ag obair",
                    "Táim ag obair",
                    "Tá mé i mo obair"
                ],
                "correctAnswer": "Bhí mé ag obair",
                "reason": "Regular verbs in the past tense get a séimhiú.",
                "state": "unanswered",
                "selectedAnswer": "",
                "category": "Eclipsis and Lenition",
                "isSubmitted": false
            },
            {
                "id": 9,
                "question": "What is the correct translation for \"Will you be there\"?",
                "choices": [
                    "An beidh tú ann?",
                    "An mbeidh tú ann?",
                    "An bhfuil tú ann?",
                    "An gbeidh tú ann?"
                ],
                "correctAnswer": "An mbeidh tú ann?",
                "reason": "Questions in future tense get an úrú.",
                "state": "unanswered",
                "selectedAnswer": "",
                "category": "Eclipsis and Lenition",
                "isSubmitted": false
            },
            {
                "id": 10,
                "question": "What is the correct translation for \"Our home?\"",
                "choices": [
                    "Ár gteach",
                    "Ár teach",
                    "Ár dteach",
                    "Ár theach"
                ],
                "correctAnswer": "Ár dteach",
                "reason": "Possessions for our, your, and plural get an úrú.",
                "state": "unanswered",
                "selectedAnswer": "",
                "category": "Eclipsis and Lenition",
                "isSubmitted": false
            }
        ]
    }
]